♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Today's
feature presentation of Glory
will not be seen.
What? Aw, I love that movie.
Aw, man, that's gonna leave
a big hole in their lineup.
What's gonna fill
the Glory hole?
In place of Glory,
we will be showing Shaft,
starring Richard Roundtree.
What? You can't just shove
Shaft in the Glory hole.
Yeah, I know. It'd
be better to put in
that movie about the two
girls who meet Nixon.
What's that movie
called? Dick?
Dick would slide right
into that Glory hole.
No, no, Dick's too short
for that Glory hole.
But if you also put in
Edward Furlong's movie, Pecker,
you got Pecker and Dick
in the Glory hole,
and you got a tight squeeze,
but it-it ought to fit.
The hell am I sitting on?
Oh, hey, that's
my old rope toy.
I was wondering
where that was.
Ew, what would you want
that for? It's gross.
No, it's not.
It's awesome.
I can suck on it
for the flavor.
I can thrash it around,
pretend it's a snake.
Sometimes I just
bite it like this.
Rope!
That's stupid.
I want it.
Well, you can't
have it; it's mine.
Oh, yeah?
Not for long it ain't.
Come on, Brian,
I need this rope
in case I open
a nautical-themed restaurant.
We got boat parts on the wall,
so you know the crab
comes from the ocean.
Eating next to a porthole!
What?!
No, no, no, no, I don't
want to make that trade.
I thought I wanted
to make that trade,
but I don't want to
make that trade.
Hey, Chris.
Where's your father?
He's still trying to get
that rope away from Brian.
He's got to give up
that obsession.
I don't like what
it's doing to him.
Precious.
Wants precious rope.
Peter, enough with
the rope.
Also wants ice cream.
No, Peter, it's too close
to dinnertime.
Get ice cream anyway.
Don't you dare.
All right,
but I'll be back in a moment
as another movie thing.
I am Johnny Five.
Need input.
Input is ice cream.
I need ice cream.
Did I say I'm
Johnny Five yet?
You didn't go
to work today, did you?
So, still got
that rope, I see.
Well, I got a
better rope.
That's not a chewing rope.
I know. It's a tying rope!
Come on, Brian,
you'd better let go.
I told you this is mine!
You're never gonna get it!
Just give me the rope.
Nobody has to get hurt, Brian.
Only one person has
to get hurt, Brian.
My teeth!
Oh! Oh, man!
I'm real sorry about
your mouth, Brian.
Damn it, Peter.
What were you thinking?
This has to be the stupidest
thing you've ever done.
No, Brian. The stupidest
thing I ever did
was turn the bubbles
off in a hot tub.
Yeah! Party!
Ew, bath with friends.
Now, remember, Brian's probably
very self-conscious
about how he looks,
so let's try to be supportive.
Brian! Dinner!
So, everybody, how was your day?
What's for dinner?
I'm starving.
My God, you look like
one of those animals.
You know, the
one that...
Which one does the
sound?
That... Aw, crap, you
know which one I mean.
Oh, who am I kidding?
You got to take me to the
dentist to get my mouth fixed.
Brian, we can try to make you
feel a little less repulsive,
but we're not spending
human money on a
deformed animal.
What? Then what am I
supposed to do?
I don't know. But here,
you can have this back.
It's boring.
It doesn't do anything.
You know what?
Go to hell, Peter!
Wow, this is
the craziest meal I've had
since I had lunch
at Tommy Sullivan's house.
Very good macaroni and
cheese, Mrs. Sullivan.
Thank you, Chris.
That was just
awful, Chris.
Terrible.
He is not ready
for flashbacks.
No, he is not.
Hey, listen,
thanks for not laying into
me like everybody else.
I don't care enough about you
to lay into you.
But now that you mention it,
your face looks like
a used condom.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, come on, Brian.
Don't do that.
Don't cry. Be a man.
I'm not crying!
Look, listen, just...
here, just take this.
What is this?
That's my dentist.
He'll bill me.
I've got an account.
You've got an account
with a dentist?
He sells me nitrous
at wholesale, I bang his wife.
Those both sound
like things for you.
Look, you want
his number or not?
I won't forget this,
Glenn Quagmire.
Don't ever say my name
like that, okay?
And don't tell anybody
about this.
Now get the hell out of the bar,
you pathetic son of a bitch.
Hey, language.
My big fat black mom is here.
I know I didn't just hear
what that man said.
Jerome, you got to go
to extra church!
Aw, Mom.
We now return to
My Dinner with Andre the Giant.
I could never give up
my electric blanket;
it's cold in New York City.
You may argue that this is
a waste of energy,
but to me, it's worth the
comfort because, let's face it,
the world is
an abrasive place.
I have maybe hours to live,
and you're wasting them.
Hey, I'm, uh...
I'm back from getting
my new teeth.
Well, come on in, Brian.
Let's see them.
All right, here it goes.
Oh, my God!
Look at your teeth!
Hey, maybe you could
help us build the dam.
If you think you got
the chops for it.
Well, think about it.
It's something to chew on.
We use him
just the right amount.
So be honest, huh?
You guys hate them.
No, Brian, are you kidding?
They're spectacular!
You look like a movie star.
Really?
Yeah, you're like an even
more handsome Adam Carolla.
God, I can't believe
you guys really like them.
Yeah, Brian, you are gonna
get so much sweet tail!
Oo-cha, oo-cha,
oo-cha, oo-cha!
Brian, you have
found your look.
That is the best cosmetic
surgery in this family
since Lois got
her boob job.
I don't know
what happened.
I told the
doctor C-cups.
I told him something else.
I think he did
a dam good job.
Okay, now we've used him
too much.
♪ When you're smiling ♪
♪ The whole world
smiles with you ♪
♪ When you're laughing ♪
♪ The sun comes
shining through ♪
♪ But when you're crying ♪
♪ You bring on the rain ♪
♪ So stop your sighing ♪
♪ Be happy again ♪
♪ Keep on smiling ♪
♪ 'Cause when you're smiling ♪
♪ The whole world
smiles with you. ♪
Oh, good, you're
already here.
I'm sorry?
Can we ask you a few questions?
Uh... yeah, sure.
Is this a good
neighborhood?
Uh, yeah,
it's a great neighborhood.
Lot of families,
good parks.
Uh, six fire hydrants,
but they are unavailable.
They are previously claimed.
They belong to some badass.
Okay, but do you think
this house will hold its value?
I don't see why not.
It's got a nice porch.
And the yard's got
plenty of room for little ones.
Although that's really
up to the two of you.
Hey, so sorry I'm late.
Let me show you the house.
No need to. Your partner
already sold us on it.
Sorry, I-I
didn't realize
they thought I was
a real estate agent.
You are a real estate agent;
you just don't know it yet.
What do you mean?
Look at that smile.
You're a born salesman.
You should
come work for me.
Huh. Never thought
I'd be in real estate.
You think I
can handle it?
Every other divorced mom
at my kid's school is a realtor.
I think you can handle it.
Bonnie, I still don't get why
you want to see this house.
The foundation is
totally out of whack.
I mean, the-the whole
house is slanting down
to that cliff
over there.
Uh-huh. Can you open
the sliding door?
I'll take it.
So tell me again,
where's the lake?
Right there.
And where's the
summer camp?
Right over there.
I'll take it.
Now, I am obligated
to disclose
that the previous owners
were murdered in this house.
Whoa, buddy!
Quit drilling; you
already struck oil.
I just don't know if this
is the right time to buy.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Maybe we should wait
till you graduate college.
Thank you, but I'm
actually 42 years old.
Uh, that's not credible.
Hello, Doctor?
I need a new pair of eyes
because clearly
mine aren't seeing straight.
You know what?
Maybe I am ready to buy.
Great! I'll get the paperwork.
Hello? Hello?
What's going on with your eyes?
Oh, uh, nothing.
Everything's fine.
Is this the guy
who wanted his pulse checked
because he died
and went to heaven?
Uh, yes.
Please stop calling.
This is a very busy
doctor's office.
♪ Where you from ♪
♪ You sexy thing ♪
♪ Sexy thing, you. ♪
Brian, five sales this week.
You're killing it.
Yeah. And last night,
I closed another big deal.
Kim in marketing.
What are the specs?
She's a two breast,
one ass fixer-upper.
The entire property was
covered in a thick brush.
Everyone in the office
besides us is garbage.
Wow, Brian, you're
doing great here.
You're really on fire.
Thanks. I guess I should
stop, drop, and roll.
Whoa.
That's enough.
The only thing is, anyone
can sell a nice house,
but a real star is someone
who can sell a dump.
I can sell anything.
Well, we got this crap
condo down by the marina.
We haven't been able to
unload it in two years.
You find some sucker to buy
it, and I'll make you partner.
All right, sounds good.
It's a plan.
Hey, did I tell you about
Kim in marketing?
You mean my wife Kim?
I'm gonna go sell
that condo.
God, there's got to be a sucker
to buy this condo.
Guys, this is on me.
I just hit 20 years in the air,
and I got a big bonus.
It's sad
when planes 'splode.
What?
Yeah, I guess.
Anyway, I am flush.
For the first time in my life,
I got money to burn.
Looks like I found my sucker.
Whoa. What?
I didn't know you worked out
at this gym, too.
Hey, Brian. Hang on,
I'm just finishing a set.
Come on, come on, two more.
Come on, come on,
you got to want it.
Nice job.
Let's get you a rubdown.
I'm glad I bumped into you
because I've been meaning
to give you something.
What's this?
That is the money you loaned me.
Oh. That's pretty cool. Thanks.
You're welcome.
I just wish I could do
something more for you.
Hmm, I could make you rich.
No, no, no, that's just money.
I'll think of something else.
What're you talking
about, Brian?
No, no, no, I've said too much.
The one thing they're pretty
firm about at the office
is you don't take
the inside deals
and give them to your friends.
What... What kind of inside
deal are you talking about?
All I can say is...
underpriced waterfront property
that's guaranteed
to appreciate in value.
That's all I can say.
Oh, wait, a-are you bothered
by sorority noise, though?
I-I don't know, Brian.
I don't know if I'm a
real estate investor.
Well, you might
surprise yourself.
I mean, I didn't think I'd ever
be friends with Ice-T.
What are you
thinkin' about?
Thinking about putting
black guy hair in a ponytail.
'Cause the times change,
but I don't.
All right, guys,
here it is.
Prescott Towers.
Quahog's premier luxury
living experience.
Nestled somewhere between the
ocean and your imagination:
Prescott Towers.
Quahog's only luxury residence
catering exclusively
to the affluent.
Affluent means rich.
Come live in the kind of place
a Persian guy would say
is a little much.
The ceiling is a pool.
Quagmire, you got to get this.
I don't know about buying
a place without seeing it first.
Of course not. I
wouldn't expect you to.
But as your friend, I wanted
to let you know early
because there's another buyer
who's about to snap it up.
I think he's a
pilot for Delta.
Delta?
It's not Lew Sheridan,
is it?
Well, I'm not really
permitted to say.
Do you like
Lew Sheridan?
I hate Lew Sheridan.
It's Lew Sheridan.
That son of a bitch!
Say what you want, but he's got
an eye for real estate. Let me
just give him a call and let him
know he's gonna get the place.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait.
Okay. I'll take it.
All right. You
won't be sorry.
Yeah, that condo
looks awesome.
You're makin'
a smart move, Quagmire.
Like I did when I wanted to
get out of that boring meeting.
Third quarter projections
indicate our sales
will be down 40%.
Why don't we go through
the profit-loss statement
line by line from
the past six quarters,
which will offer us a good
cost analysis comparison
that I think we'll
be able to utilize
as we move forward - Aah!
into the next fiscal year.
Hey, guys,
I got to leave.
I got a nosebleed,
and, uh, I don't work here.
All right, Quagmire,
now when you introduce us
to the ladies
by the pool,
I'm a millionaire,
Joe's a war hero,
and Cleveland
is Magic Johnson.
I own a lot
of theaters.
I hope you don't know
much else about me.
Is this the right address?
This doesn't look
like the building
from Brian's presentation.
Come on, Quagmire.
Never judge a book
by its cover.
Or a movie.
No.
It's probably nothing,
but there's a stain on the rug
in the shape of a little kid.
I don't know if
you want this now,
but I bought you
a mini cactus.
What the hell?
This is a dump.
Well, maybe it's still
got a nice ocean view.
The harbor is poisoned.
Damn it.
Brian screwed me.
That's why I've never made any
major investments with my dog.
What am I gonna do?
I sank my entire bonus
into this place.
Let me see your
contract, Quagmire.
There's got to be
a way out of this.
I'm gonna kill him,
that's what I'm gonna do.
ClubAmigos.
That's what we're gonna
call this place.
Here it is. You've got
72 hours after closing
to rescind the
purchase. State law.
Thank God. I got to go
tell Brian the deal's off.
Oh, there's a head
in the freezer.
Ooh, and sherbert.
We're looking for
Brian Griffin.
I'm still within 72 hours,
and I want
to get out of my contract.
You'd have to speak to
Mr. Griffin about that.
But I'm sorry, he's
not in the office.
Where the hell is he?
Slow down, Quagmire.
This sounds like
a discussion to have
over a cone-shaped cup of water.
Ah.
You can drink from these
and then put 'em on your head
to be a clown
from an Italian opera.
♪ Laughing outside,
crying down below ♪
♪ Pasta, meatballs,
Joe DiMaggio ♪
♪ Fellatio, Pinocchio,
a pizza pie from Domino's ♪
♪ All of this because
I'm singing in a pointy hat. ♪
Look, Mr. Griffin's not here,
but if you leave your name,
I'll let him know
you stopped by.
Fine. Glenn Quagmire.
Have him call me
the minute he gets in.
They're gone.
Well, for the next 72 hours,
I'm gonna be harder to find
than a nice cat.
You need me to clean out
your litter box?
Mittens.
Okay, Rupert, we're
going to play a game.
I'm gonna be Buffalo Bill,
and you're gonna be
a great big fat person.
Close the lid.
Brian? What are you doing?
I'm hiding from Quagmire
for a few more hours.
After that, he won't be able
to pull out of that deal.
Well, if anybody knows how
to pull out, it's Quagmire.
I have a lot of fun
up here in my room.
Welcome home.
Aah! Hey-Hey,
there, buddy.
There you are. I've been
looking all over for you.
That's why you've been
hiding from me in this motel?
Now let me out of this deal
and give me my money back.
Look, i-if you're not happy
with your current property,
we could roll
your money over
into something in
Sinkhole Estates.
Those places are going
very fast, though.
Who's a pilot you hate?
You are such a scumbag.
You know, when you were poor,
you were always a douche,
but at least you
came by it honestly.
But now, screwing over
the people who helped you?
I don't know how
you sleep at night.
My God.
You're right.
I'm a jerk.
I'm a selfish
and pretentious jerk.
And you're
the only guy in town
who's ever called me out
on my crap.
You know, I used to hate you
for it, but...
now I think
you're the only person
who was trying
to be my friend.
No, I think you're
misunderstanding me.
No, I'm serious.
Even though I know
you never liked me,
you still helped me
when I really needed it.
That says a lot
about your character.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Because I am none
of the things you are.
You're honest, and direct,
and compassionate,
and...
that is 72 hours.
Enjoy your craphole, dumbass.
You son of a bitch!
Wow, so I guess
that's it for you
and real estate,
huh, Brian?
Yeah, it was a lot
tougher than I thought.
Oh, yeah, it's real hard
being a real estate agent.
I mean, you got to be
able to count bathrooms.
I once beat a real estate agent
in a game of chess.
Me. A well-known buffoon.
Face it,
you failed
at people's
safety net job.
Oh, come on, guys.
Give me a break, huh?
I've had a
rough day.
You've had
a rough day?
You guys wouldn't
believe the day I've had.
First of all, I didn't have any
clean underwear this morning,
so I had to wear
a bathing suit.
Then I missed the bus,
of course. Then it looked like
it was gonna start to rain.
Luckily, it didn't.
And like that wasn't enough,
then we had a pop quiz in history.
Oh, European history. American
history was last year. Then...
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru